Hello!
This time, I'm at Iwaki station in my hometown.
Hashigo-zake!
Yay!
I'm really looking forward to this second local ladashi-zake!
YYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY
I'll do this!
First stop is Akaoni-san!
Thank you for your hard work!
My dad said he's been there before!
Oh no, Poli Poli station!
I went to see "Umizaru" 7 times!
I went to see Umizaru seven times.
Same Umizaru.
It's like 4:00 a.m. now.
It's so good!
What's this?
What the hell?
Maybe I'll live here.
Found it!
It's the Red Devil.
Ta-da!
It's the Red Devil!
We're here! We're here, Red Devil!
Is that Super Dry or Kirin Classic?
Grainger, I prefer Super Dry. Can I have a bottle of Super Dry?
A bottle of beer.
Asahi?
Yes, please wait.
Momogen's nice.
I'm back. I can't believe you're finally home.
Peach Blossom, you've been so consistent this time. I'll have the first one.
Peach Blast!
Oh, no! Even when I drank beer, I was still pee-pee-pee!
It wasn't just Hyrule!
I didn't expect it to be pee even when I drank a bottle of beer!
Seriously? Are you kidding?
You mean he's a one-track mind?
He's a pattern person.
The yakitori... my dad says it's delicious.
Here.
And shiitake mushrooms...
I can't think of anything else.
Nogu shiitake.
He's saying it so well.
I thought nothing of it.
With my head
Head...
In the head.
Yes?
You know, with a plate like this.
It's not a plate. What's this?
I want to drink from a glass.
I'd like to drink from a glass.
It's a skewer.
I wonder if it's a frog at night.
That one's cute.
Which one is it?
That feels good.
Maybe it's supposed to be cute.
Is that a snake?
What? What snake?
What? They have them now?
You're kind of cute in reverse.
What? Why is it a snake?
Rabbits are cuter.
Dogs and cats are cuter.
Why a snake?
Snake coordinates that swallow up the other person whole
From the nuance of making any round part of the partner fit the whole body.
Snake cage
Let's change it up today... and call it "Hebika".
Let's change our current action, Hebika!
Mozuku
Sashiara-san also found out on YouTube that mozuku is good before eating.
I'm going to buy a lot of mozuku!
Thanks to Sashiara-san, I'm going to eat it!
Thanks to Sashiara-san, I'm eating mozuku!
It's so sour!
What do you think?
Snake?
I'm sorry.
Can we have a bottle of beer, please?
Thank you all for your comments.
I really appreciate all the warm comments.
I didn't think you'd come so often.
It's better than I thought it would be.
And what's more, people who probably don't even know how much I know... have come to know me.
There's a person like him!
Such a person!
But I was so happy to hear that some of them drank dinner with this.
Well, I'm going to have a glass of wine now.
Thank you all for your hard work today.
Cheers!
How was your day?
I see.
Good job.
Are we done?
We're done.
Your mimicry was amazing.
I really laughed out loud when I saw that from Hana-chan.
Finally...
Hana-chan's sister said they looked alike.
That's why I'm already happy.
There are five of us.
Hana-chan was eating that, eating shiitake mushrooms and stuff.
She said they were delicious.
I thought, "That looks just like my imitation!
But it's been a hit, so I hope you'll do it again today.
Of course.
But it's not an impersonation.
It's just coming down.
Thank you very much.
Shiitake mushrooms!
Oh no, more than Noguchi's coming
Here come the head and the big shiitake mushrooms!
huh?
Well then...
I'll just lean down like a normal person.
Please do!
I'll put it on once.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good work, Noguchi-san.
I heard today that you like shiitake mushrooms.
Yes, yes, yes.
I prepared shiitake mushrooms for you.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
When was the first time you served shiitake mushrooms?
Yesterday.
I'll have some today.
Happy, happy, happy.
I'm so happy.
Bon appétit!
So this is the official version.
This is un-official Yuu-chan!
Shiitake shiitake shiitake!
Wow!
Yum!
That's me... that's me right here.
Thank you very much.
It's good.
Isn't it big? Oh, man.
You know what I mean? Can you feel it?
It's a big party.
But shiitake mushrooms are really...
I like them because of you.
Thank you, Iyori!
Wasabi.
How is it? I like it.
I used to not be able to eat tai, but now I can.
As an adult, you can eat more things, right?
Yes, I like it.
I couldn't eat shiitake mushrooms, I couldn't eat melon, I couldn't eat Neapolitan, I couldn't eat shwarmite...
I can eat everything. But milk is the only thing I can't stand.
I don't like this kind of person! I don't like this kind of person!
Tell me, what's the highest value?
He's as good as Shohei Otani selling home runs!
Uko!
I had a special AFM called "Hand in Hand".
I have a radio show on a special AFM called Hand in Hand.
I'm in Fukushima now, and I'm here in Iwaki.
I'm here in Iwaki, Fukushima, and this is what I've been doing after I've finished my work.
I've been dying.
So I'll see you soon.
Good night.
If that's the case, I have something to report about my addiction...
UNO!
Yay!
But I don't have UNO cards because I play on an app.
But I wanted to play UNO with everyone, so I bought UNO cards.
So, the next day, I went to the oden shop to bring the cards with me.
I left my UNO cards and all the Crayon Shin-chan stuff I bought that day at the oden shop.
On the train
I got off the train quickly because I thought I didn't have the bag, so I called the store and went there, but I forgot something.
The clerk asked me, "What did you forget? I'm sorry, sir.
He said, "UNO, Crayon Shin-chan." He looked inside and found out I was Crayon Shin-chan.
I'm a VIP member, so I play UNO every day, and I have the UNO app.
At first you get dealt cards, you know, randomly, and if you don't get a good card...
I thought, "I can't win with this card.
But you never know what life has in store for you.
Sometimes you can win with a bad card.
You never know what life has in store for you.
Life is like UNO
That's deep.
There is a UNO button on the last card.
If you don't press the UNO button
it will say "caught" and your card will be increased.
So don't miss the chance.
You have to miss it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Press the UNO button on your life.
Excuse me, sir.
Kitchum soda pop
Kitcheom Kitcheom!
I'm Kitcheom!
Can I live a great life?
Debut of Shochu
It's a sweet potato!
I can drink shochu!
I can drink shochu with sweetpotato.
It's kind of cool.
I thought it was cool.
I knew it was from sweetpotato.
I didn't think it would be that bad.
It's easier to drink than if you don't.
Okay, then.
Hey, Anna.
I can't imagine you eating raw fish.
I'm just imagining it.
I'd like to see Anna say she hasn't eaten raw fish in a long time.
I'd like to meet Anna.
Here's some delicious raw fish from Fukushima.
Impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible!
Octopus, tuna, bonito and pie!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Impossible, impossible.
But...
Octopus.
I might be able to go for octopus.
Impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible.
But...
But it's work.
It's work.
Bon appétit.
How was the octopus? Anne.
I can't, but...
You don't really look like him.
You really don't look like him.
I can only sing like that.
I'm sorry, but I love you.
I was signing autographs the other day.
He said he was free and he'd help me.
I signed your book.
And then...
He asked me to scatter them.
Like a manager.
I said, "Okay, I'm not busy.
And I didn't even ask him to do it.
Our leader's a good guy.
I think it's time to move on to the second house.
I'd like to call my family and ask them for a recommendation for a second place.
I'd like to call my family and ask them for recommendations for a good second place.
Pabbie.
Hello?
I'm having a drink in Iwaki for some sort of hagashi-zake project.
Is there a good place to go for the second round of drinks?
Eh, I'll go there anyway.
Okay, thanks, bye!
Hi, bye-bye!
My dad told me about this place.
I'd like to go to the second restaurant, SHUN.
End of the first shop
So the first house is over!
But not at all, how many drinks have we had now?
Bottled beer, bottled beer, shochu, I can go on and on!
What a nice atmosphere!
Some kind of fish from Iwaki city!
Haaaaaa!
Wait, I might be able to eat a blowfish
I'd like to go to Shun-san!
So, Shun-san
It was full!
Popular!
Please, everyone, please go there when you come to Iwaki!
Well, there are so many!
That's Hashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo, Kashizo
I'm stoned! - I'm stoned!
That's the good thing about Hashi-zoo!
This is Iwaki Market
I came to Iwaki Market I want to drink outside
I want to drink outside. Oden shop here?
I'm going to go have a drink.
The second restaurant, Passion Izakaya.
Come to Jajauma, Jajauma, Jajauma!
Wait, listen.
I think it's gonna be okay. I think it's gonna be okay.
Geordaise, Geordaise, it's Mr. Sachalo.
Oh!
Ha! It's fate!
Are you musicians?
Musicians!
Suddenly, the moment I walked in, I thought there was such a thing.
So, for the second house, I'd like to decide on the first drink at the corner. I'd like to settle for a corner cup.
I'm so happy because I really like to drink outside.
I'm curious about the gari-hi ball, though.
Gari-hi is delicious.
Eh, so to gari high, do you recommend gari high?
I love Gari! Well, I'll have a Gari highball.
Well, you know...
Dad's here, too.
He's going to have a drink with us.
He rushed in... rushed in, like he's here to help.
He said, "Dad, I'm here to help you.
I can't hear or see him, but...
But he's here....
We drink around here.
He's gesturing.
He's over there.
What? That way?
But I always drink this way.
Your father drinks.
I don't know.
There's a cat here.
I think there's a cat in here.
Hello.
I'm from Iwaki.
Sorry, I'm not a stranger.
Believe me!
I'm from Iwaki
I'm from Iwaki.
Let's drink together.
What do you want?
It's on me.
I was rejected.
I'm going to have a drink.
I'll have a gari gari.
It smells like sushi.
It's sushi!
Cheers! Here's your gari-hai.
It's the best drink I've ever had... and I've never had a drink that made me feel so guilty.
It's like this snack sana.
Guilty pleasures are the best kind of sake.
They'll use it. What is it? It's hard to tell.
I'll recommend something for Kihara-chan.
But we'll buy it.
Maika!
I'd like you to recommend some salted fish.
Shiokara?
Have some shiokara, Chara-chan.
I don't eat shiokara.
Eat it!
I really can't eat shiokara, I really can't.
I'll eat it.
Come on!
Bon appétit!
Maybe I can't eat it!
Eat honey, eat honey, eat honey, eat honey.
Is it good? Cawacko!
Delicious!
That was the best theater ever.
I'm sorry.
I'll have another one!
This is a sake from Iwaki City, Fukushima Prefecture!
Sake!
I'll start with sake and salt!
It's the best combination!
Sake is always better with something with a little bit of a kick!
Sake is so good!
Pyah!
I love it!
It was Pia's sake drinking day!
I want you to drink with the other members...
Oh, there you are!
Sashiara-san and...
Oh, Sashiara-san!
I wanted to have a drink with Sashiara-san.
This Kashigo-zake project is really popular.
If it goes a million rounds...
Wow!
Sashiarasan and drinking with Sashiarasan
If you really want to see a certain kind of drinking
Please do 1,000,000 rounds!
1,000 times per person per day!
Please watch it.
Also, I want to drink with Yuki Kashiwagi.
I talked to her once at Snack Sana.
It was the first time we really talked.
I didn't even let her buy me a drink.
She was amazing.
What was that? Was this Kashiwagi-san's concert? I thought so.
It was so amazing.
I was captivated by Yukirin.
I was hooked.
Every cell in my body was hooked.
I understood why she's been an idol for so long.
I understand why she's so loved.
I'm hooked.
I think I might've gotten carried away.
Yeah.
Hashtag Yukirin-san.
Please have a drink with me someday! I'm eagerly awaiting it!
I'm eagerly awaiting it.
I'd love to hear a lot of Yukirin's stories.
I'd like to hear a lot of your stories.
It was an interesting episode.
A fan told me that Sanatsu's father was there, even though he didn't disclose his face.
I said, "Why didn't you tell the public?
I said, "Why didn't you disclose that?
His mother was there.
I want to wear that badge on my backpack.
I mean, he loves me, but his mom comes over to our house for Equal Love Tea, and he's my dad's badge dad.
My dad is the badge dad.
Shoko at karaoke.
Like Shoko at karaoke with Maika and Sana.
Shoko was in the middle and Maika and Sanah were beside her.
Together
Maika and Sana sang "Niji no moto" together.
When Maika and Sana sang together, she said, "My ears are so happy! She said, "My ears are happy!
She said her ears were happy.
And then we all sang together.
"I want to be by your side" and "Sunflower Promise.
The three of us?
The three of us.
Shoko, you know... when she gets a little drunk...
I don't know what the fans think of me, but...
She lightens up a lot.
I think the group lights up together.
We have a lot of fun when we drink together.
I'd like to continue drinking with the members in the future.
I don't know if I can show you the contents of my voice.
I think drinking with the members is a good idea.
I recommend it!
I don't think I can show it to you yet, but I'm going to recreate it by imitating you.
So please be imaginative!
It's warm.
Is this the back menu?
Yes, it is.
I got the back menu.
Thanks to my dad, we've got the back menu.
I think it's outrageously delicious.
Outrageously delicious? I don't know.
I'll eat too much because my dad might get mad at me.
He'll never find out.
Well, then, I'll just have a bowl of this ridiculously delicious jarred noodle soup, Monohassam.
Bon appétit!
Well, but, yeah.
I'd say it's delicious, but it's like... A little thick? Flat noodles?
200% thicker.
Well, it can't be that good.
Oh, my God, it's so funny.
It really wasn't funny.
I'm not funny when I'm drunk.
So he's funny too?
You're not funny? I've been a funny representative my whole life.
Can I say it again?
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Can I describe the taste?
Please.
For example.
When rice scores a goal.
It's that good.
Can you afford it?
What did you do?
Minus 25.
That's a heebie-jeebies, right?
So...
It's time for Iwaki's Hashigo-zake, the closing rattle!
It's still a little early in the day.
I have to go home tomorrow because I have to work and the last train is about to leave.
I have to go home.
And I've done a million rounds!
I heard that you and Sashiara-san are going to have a photo project.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll write every day.
Write every day!
Let's write every day!
It's really good!
Wow, it's great.
Okay, you write it down.
Sure. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Great. It was a flop.